♪♪～
Buy them fast, buy them now!
（ライラ）さあ　買った　買った～！→
We've got fresh Hami melons, white apricots, and dates!
新鮮なハミウリ
白杏子　ナツメヤシ→
この町じゃ
採れないものばかりだよ！
All rarities not found in this town!
（サアサ）ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much!
You with the kabob! Want to try something much tastier?
（ライラ）カバブのおにいさん
口直しに　どう？→
And you, guy with the flushed cheeks! You can turn this into alcohol too!
そっちの
飲んだくれの　おじいちゃん→
これ　酒にできるよ。
Sahsa, our next batch still isn't here?
次の荷は　まだか？　サアサ。
早くしないと売り切れちまうぞ。
At this rate, we're going to sell out before we can restock!
She'll be back with it at any moment now.
今　まとめて運ばれてくるわ。
あっ　ほら！
Look!
（ライラ）あっ　ははっ！　お前が
うちのキャラバンに入ってくれて→
I'm so glad you joined our caravan, Morgiana!
本当によかったよ　モルジアナ。
（モルジアナ）はい。
I see.
It's already been half a year since we met you in Qishan, hasn't it?
（サアサ）チーシャンで
モルジアナと会ってから→
もう半年たつのね。
I apologize for my behavior back then.
あのときは　すみませんでした。
I had heard you were headed for Balbadd and I jumped in front of your caravan without a second thought.
バルバッドへ向かう
キャラバンと聞いて→
思わず　馬車の前に
飛び出してしまったのです。
Thank you so much for taking in a complete stranger like myself.
見ず知らずの私を
乗せてくださって→
本当に　感謝しております。
（ライラ）いや　いいって…。
I-It's fine.
モルジアナは
とっても働き者だしな。
You're such a hard worker!
Yes. We wouldn't mind if you continued to stay with us, even after Balbadd!
そうよ。
バルバッドまでと言わず→
このまま
ずっと　うちにいてもいいのよ。
I cannot.
いえ。　私は　故郷へ帰ります。
I must return to my homeland.
That is what I promised my benefactor.
それが私の恩人との約束ですから。
akogare wo ima tsukanda
My desires are within reach.
♪♪～
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
ashita kara umare kawaru toka
People say they'll change the next day.
♪♪～
dareka ga mikiri tsuketa toka
But they give up so easily.
kono machi no style toka
That's just how it is here.
sonna mono ni nagasare tsuzukete
They get swept away by those excuses day by day.
kado no toreta genseki ni ha
They're nothing more than a chip, swept off the edge
kitto daremo you ha nai
and no longer needed by anyone.
♪♪～
fushigi to tobira no mukou ni ha
Guess what? Out there,
v.i.p nanoru yatsu ha naku
no one's swaggering around like a VIP.
daremo ga kunou no hate sa ore mo
Everyone suffers their own heartaches, myself included.
akogare wo ima tsukanda
But my desires are within reach.
♪♪～
mi wo yudanereba ii  kaji ha kono te ni
Throw yourself in with abandon. I've got the wheel.
mitsu kazoete the show time
On the count of three, it's show time!
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
♪♪～
6th Night
Fanalis, the Warrior Tribe
あっ。
あぁ…。
♪♪～
What happened here?
（サアサ）何かあったのかしら？
≫コツ　コツ…（足音）
What's going on?
（ライラ）どうしたんだ？
バルバッドの内紛で→
Rogue thieves have invaded our city
because of the internal strife in Balbadd.
盗賊崩れのゴロツキが
町に　流れ込んできてるんだ。→
I suggest you guys get out of here as quickly as you can too.
お前たちも　早いとこ
出発した方がいいぜ。
Leila...
ライラ…。
盗賊崩れなんか　怖くはないさ。
There's no reason to fear a few rogue thieves!
気にせず　商売しようぜ。
うっ！　いってぇな。
Let's do business as usual.
That hurt!
どこに目ぇ付けてんだよ！　あっ…。
Watch where you're going!
My, what a vulgar little girl.
（ファティマー）
あらやだ　下品なお嬢さんね。
♪♪～
（ライラ）奴隷商人…。
（サアサ）かわいそうに。→
A slave merchant...
Those poor people.
どうして
奴隷なんて制度があるのかしら。
Why is a practice like slavery allowed?
♪♪～
I hate these marks...
嫌だな　このアザ。
I wish they'd hurry up and disappear.
早く消えてくれないかな。
Who came up with the idea to bind people in chains anyway.
人間を鎖でつなぐなんて
誰が　思いついたのかしら。
はぁ　はぁ　はぁ　はぁ…。
♪♪～
（ジャミル）ダメじゃないか　モルジアナ。
You've been a bad girl, Morgiana.
僕から　逃げられるとでも
思ったのかい？→
Did you really think you could run away from me?
No matter how far you run, you'll always be my slave.
どこへ逃げても
お前は　僕の奴隷なんだ。→
一生　鎖で縛り続けてやる。
I'll keep you chained forever.
ふふふふっ。
嫌っ…　助けて。
No... Someone, save me!
誰か…。
（ジャミル）ははははっ！
Please!
誰か～～!!
はっ！　はぁ　はぁ…。
はぁ…。
（ライラ）大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
You were making noises in your sleep.
うなされていたぞ。
I apologize.
すみません。
怖い夢を見ていました。
I was having a nightmare.
（ライラ）そういうときは
いい薬草がある。　待ってな。
I have a good herbal remedy for that.
Give me just a moment.
えっと　確か　ここに…。
I think I put it in here...
本当に…→
Thank you...
Thank you so very much.
ありがとうございます。
（ライラ）だから　それは　もういいって。
No, please, I said it's fine!
We're friends journeying together on a caravan.
同じキャラバンの仲間なんだから。
それに　私だって
ここじゃ　モルジアナと同じ→
And besides, I'm not much different from you. I was picked up by this caravan too.
キャラバンに　拾われた身だし。
Huh?
えっ？
あっ　あった。　これ　これ。→
Here it is!
Just what I was looking for.
To put it in your words, my "benefactor" is Sahsa.
まっ　そういう意味じゃ
私の恩人は　サアサだよな。→
She found me collapsed in the desert and saved me.
砂漠で
行き倒れてた私を　助けてくれた。
Her and a mysterious young boy.
それと
もう一人　あの不思議な少年。
不思議な少年？
話しても→
Mysterious young boy?
I doubt you'd believe me even if I told you!
モルジアナは
きっと信じないだろうなぁ。
でも　そんなふうに　いろんな人に
助けられてきたから→
But the point is, I'm only here because of the help I've received from so many different people.
私は　ここにいる。　だから→
That's why it's my turn to protect them now.
今度は　私が　サアサと
このキャラバンの仲間たちを→
守る番なんだ。
ふふっ　ありがとう。
Thanks.
（ライラ）あっ！
なんだよ…　聞いてたのかよ。
What?! You were listening?
（サアサ）
聞かなくても　分かっていたわ。→
I didn't hear anything I didn't know already.
ライラは　本当に優しいね。
You're sweet, Leila.
I am not.
そんなことないよ。
それに　正義感があって→
You have a strong sense of right and wrong, and you care deeply for your friends.
仲間思い。
だから　そんなことないって！
I said I don't!
ふふふっ　てれてもダメよ。
You're blushing.
（ライラ）てれてない。
（サアサ）本当に？
I am not!
Really?
（ライラ）もう寝る！
（サアサ）ふふふっ。
I'm going to sleep!
What? We're not going to Balbadd?
えっ？　バルバッドには
行かないんですか？
うむ。　バルバッドへの一本道に→
A band of thieves has set up camp on the only road leading into Balbadd.
盗賊団が
住み着いてしまったんだ。→
我々は
別ルートを行くことにした。
We've decided to take a different path.
You were aiming to go to Balbadd in
order to return to your homeland, right?
モルジアナは　故郷へ帰るため→
バルバッドを
目指しているんだったな？
はい。　バルバッドからしか
船が出ていなくて…。
Yes.
The ships that will take me home leave only from Balbadd.
Are there no other routes you can take?
ほかに　ルートはないのかね？
Where is your homeland?
故郷は　どこなんだ？
You don't need to say.
まあいい…。　その盗賊団は→
That band of thieves is rumored to be extremely vicious and cruel.
相当　凶暴らしくてな。
私の友人のキャラバンも襲われて→
They assaulted my friend's caravan and many caravan members lost their lives.
隊員を　何人か失ったという。
だから　諦めておくれ。
あの道は通れない。
We cannot take that path. I'm sorry.
But what if...
でも　もし…。
ん？
Yes?
If someone were to defeat those thieves, then that path would be open once again, right?
もし
誰かが　その盗賊団を倒せば→
道は　通れるようになりますよね？
（ファティマー）どう？　いい砦でしょ？
What do you think?
It's a perfect fortress, isn't it?
（Ｓナンド）いや～　まったくです
ファティマーさん。→
Just perfect, Mister Fatima!
You really don't mind if us thieves use it as our base?
こんなすばらしい砦を
我が盗賊団のアジトに→
使わせてもらえるとは。
（ファティマー）いいのよ。
Of course. This arrangement is profitable for me as well.
おかげで　私も　もうかってるから。
Thieves and slave traders are a perfect
combo. We need to help each other out!
（Ｓナンド）盗賊と奴隷商人は
持ちつ持たれつですな～。→
This fortress is seriously perfect. The guards are always so bored because no one can get in!
それにしても　砦が　堅牢すぎて
警備が　暇で暇で。
♪♪～
≪（盗賊たち）ははははっ！
（盗賊）んっ？
（盗賊）なんだ？　おい。
♪♪～
盗賊団の皆さん→
Excuse me, thieves.
I have something to ask all of you.
少々お話があるのですが。
あん？
Would you please leave this area?
ここから
出ていってもらえませんか？
（盗賊）ああっ？
今　なんつった？　お嬢ちゃん。
What did you say, missy?
ここから出ていってくださいと。
Please leave here.
道が通れなくて
とても迷惑しています。
No one is able to use this path because of your presence here.
If you will not go, I will forcibly evacuate you.
ダメなら…
力ずくで立ち退いていただきます。
（一同）あはははっ！
Those are big words coming from such a small girl.
おもしれぇ　お嬢ちゃんだな。
Why don't you try "evacuating" me?
それじゃあ
おじちゃんで試してみるかい？
ひひひひっ！
ドゴッ！
（盗賊）がっ…。
うおっ…　ううっ…。
あっ…。
くっ！　このガキ～！
You punk!
♪♪～
≪（盗賊たち）うわっ！
ん？
んん～？　なんだ？　騒がしいな。
What's this? It's quite noisy outside tonight.
ドゴッ！
おおっ…。
♪♪～
うおぉ～！
あっ…。　ぐわっ！
うおっ！
うわっ…。
はあぁ～！
うわっ！
あっ…。
（Ｌナンド）どけ～！→
Move it!
I'll take her.
俺がやる。
♪♪～
死ね～！　このガキ～！
Die, you brat!
ふっ！
バキッ！
あの赤髪　強靭な脚力→
Her red hair! Her powerful legs!
Her feral fighting style!
獣のような戦いぶり→
間違いない　あの少女は…。
She must be one of them!
はあ～！
（Ｌナンド）ぐわっ！
The rulers of the Dark Continent,
（ファティマー）暗黒大陸の覇者→
最強の戦闘民族ファナリス！
the powerful warrior tribe, the Fanalis!
≪（Ｌナンド）うわっ…。
（ファティマー）ねえ　頭領さん。
Hey Chief.
おっ。
あの子　欲しいわ。　もらっていい？
I want that girl.
Can I take her?
あっ　あっ…。　ひぃ～！
頭領は　どこですか？
Where is your leader?
あっ！
カァーー！（砂漠カラスの鳴き声）
カァー！　カァー！
（ファティマー）よけるなんて　さすがね。
あっ。
Impressive. You were able to dodge its attack.
I'm so glad to meet you, girl of the Fanalis.
お目に掛かれて　うれしくてよ→
ファナリスのお嬢さん。
あなたが　盗賊団の頭領ですか？
Are you the leader of this band of thieves?
（ファティマー）嫌ぁ～ね。
盗賊なんかと　一緒にしないでよ。
Oh no! Don't lump me in with the likes of them.
私は　奴隷商人よ。
はっ！
I'm a slave trader.
♪♪～
昨日の…。
The one from yesterday...
なら　早く　頭領を呼んで。
If you're not the leader, then get him.
さもないと…。
さもないと？
Or else!
Or else?
Or else I'll...
さもないと…　あっ。
♪♪～
What...
あれ？
It's finally taking effect, I see.
やっと効いてきたようね。→
This is a desert crow. Its claws hold
poison powerful enough to fell a bull.
牛をも眠らせる
砂漠カラスの爪の毒。
♪♪～
Operation "Capture the Fanalis": Success.
（ファティマー）捕獲完了。→
Sleep well, my dear.
おやすみ　お嬢ちゃん。
きゃあ～！
（ジャミル）ぐっ！→
Stop!
んんっ！→
Please!
ふん！　ぐっ！→
痛いか？　モルジアナ。→
Does it hurt, Morgiana?
That's what you get for trying to run away from me!
僕から逃げようなんて
考えるからだ。→
You're a slave.
お前は　奴隷だ。
その鎖があるかぎり→
As long as you wear those chains, you will never be able to escape!
どこへも逃げられないんだよ。
嫌っ…　やめて…。　助けて…。
No, stop...
Save me!
（ナージャ）おねえちゃん　大丈夫？
Are you okay?
（ナージャ）私は　ナージャっていうの。
My name's Nadja.
I used to live in Balbadd with my mommy and my daddy, but I was caught by a scary man.
お母さんとお父さんと
バルバッドに住んでたんだけど→
怖いおじさんたちに
捕まっちゃって。
そうですか。
I see.
These shackles are so strong.
（心の声）≪なんて頑丈な足かせ≫
Miss?
（ナージャ）おねえちゃん。
あっ。
私たち
これから　どうなっちゃうの？
What's going to happen to us?
We'll be forced into slavery.
奴隷にされます。
えっ？
What?
私たちを捕まえたのは
奴隷商人ですので→
The ones who caught us are slave traders.
このままだと　私たちは→
Therefore, if we stay here, we will be sold as slaves.
奴隷にされてしまいます。
奴隷って？
まず　奴隷市場で裸にされ→
What are slaves?
First, we will be taken to a slave auction where we will
be forced to strip naked and watch as people bet on us.
競売に掛けられます。
そして　見知らぬ土地に売られ→
Then we will be sold off to some unknown land.
そこで鎖を付けられて
死ぬまで働くことになります。
And there, we will be forced to work the rest of our lives in chains.
If we try to run, we will be whipped.
逃げようとすれば　鞭打ち。
そのほか　恐ろしい罰を→
The punishments are dreadful and horrendous.
受けることになります。
うぅ～…。→
ううっ…　うぅ…。
Mommy... Daddy...
お父さん　お母さん→
怖いよ…。　うぅ　ううっ…。
I'm scared.
（回想）((うぅ　ううっ…))
((お父さん　お母さん　怖いよ…))
Mommy... Daddy... I'm scared.
Where are you?
≪どこにいるの？
助けて…　助けて！≫
Save me!
（ナージャ）ううっ…　うぅ…。
んん…　うぅ…。　あっ。
I-I-It's okay.
あっ　いえ　その…　大丈夫です。
Don't worry, you won't become a slave.
やっぱり
あなたは　奴隷にはなりません。
I'll find a way to escape from here.
なぜなら
私が　隙を見て　ここから逃げます。
そのとき
あなたと　あなたのご両親を→
When I do, I'll take you and your parents with me.
連れていきます。
本当に？
Really?
ふふっ。　本当です。
Yes, really.
私が　絶対に
なんとかしますから→
I'll definitely save you.
You won't have to be a slave.
あなたは　奴隷にはなりません。
信じてください。
うん。
Please trust me.
Okay.
ふふっ。
Morgiana!
（ライラ）モルジアナ！　モルジアナ！
やっぱり　どこにもいない。
もしかして　一人でバルバッドへ!?
I can't find her anywhere!
Do you think she went to Balbadd by herself?
でも　途中には
盗賊団のアジトがあるんじゃ…。
But what about the band of thieves blocking the way?
くそ～！　助けに行かねぇと！
Darn it all!
I've got to go help her!
Wait!
待て！
なんで止めるんだ！
Why are you stopping me?
仲間が　危険な目に
遭ってるかもしれないんだぞ！
Our friend could be in danger right this minute!
あっ。
（ナージャ）はぁ　はぁ　はぁ…。
ん？　あっ。
はぁ　はぁ　はぁ…。
すごい熱。
She's burning up!
どなたか…
どなたか来てください！
Someone... Someone, please help!
はぁ　はぁ…。
（ファティマー）
あら　舌の根まで腫らして…。→
My, her tongue is swollen all the way up to her tonsils.
こらダメね。
えっ？
She's no good.
But talk about perfect timing.
（ファティマー）でも　ちょうどよかった。
The desert hyenas just ran out of food.
砂漠ハイエナの餌が
切れてたのよ。
ガウッ！　ガウッ！　ガウッ！
（ナージャ）あっ　あっ…。
No! Someone help me!
嫌っ…　助けて…。
I don't believe in providing treatment for low-grade slaves.
（ファティマー）うちはねぇ
価値の低い奴隷の手当ては→
しないの。　だって
薬代が　もったいないじゃない。→
It's just not worth the money, you know?
ふふふふっ。　だからね→
So I use those slaves as food.
そういう奴隷は　餌にするのよ。
This timing is just too perfect. Make sure you pay close attention.
いい機会だから
あなたも　よ～く見てなさい→
奴隷が　どういうものかを。
きゃあ～！
This is a slave!
ガウッ！
やめろ～～!!
Stop it!
ガン！　ガン！
外れないわよ。→
Those won't come off.
I had those shackles specially made.
その足かせは　特別製だもの。
ぐっ！　はぁ　はぁ…。
≪外れない≫
They won't break.
I promised her I'd save her!
≪絶対に助けるって
約束したのに…≫
((無理だ　無理。
お前の鎖は　ず～っと一生→
It's pointless. You'll never be able to get rid of your chains.
絶対に　外すことはできない))
They'll be there for life!
（ゴルタスの声）本当か？　モルジアナ。
Is that true, Morgiana?
あっ！　誰!?
Who was that?
Is that the extent of your power?
（ゴルタスの声）
君の力は　そんなものか？→
You can't even break one pair of leg shackles?
その足かせを
外すこともできないのか？
♪♪～
ピィ　ピィ　ピィ　ピィ…（ルフの声）
You should already be free from your chains, Morgiana.
（ゴルタスの声）
君の鎖は　もう取れたはずだよ→
モルジアナ。→
You are no longer the slave you were in the past.
君は　もう昔とは違う。→
奴隷の身分から　解放された。→
You've been freed.
君を　本当に縛っていたものは
もう何一つない。→
There is nothing left tying you down.
ただ　過去の恐怖だけだ。→
Except your own fear of the past.
And those chains are easily broken with a blade of courage.
そして
それは　勇気で　簡単に断ち切れる。
ふふふふっ！
きゃあ～～!!　うっ！
くっ！
（ファティマー）ああっ！
That's right, Morgiana.
（ゴルタスの声）そうだ　モルジアナ。→
There is not a single thing in this world that can chain you down!
君を縛るものなど→
この世に　何一つない！
はあぁ～～！
バキン！
♪♪～
すぅ～～…。
うわっ！　なんなのよ!?　あの子！
What is she doing?
キャイン　キャイン　キャイン…
ふん！
バキン！
It's all okay now.
もう大丈夫よ。
さあ　早く　ここから逃げましょう。
Hurry, let's leave this place.
ううっ…。
くっ…。
競売用のあれを　全部出しなさい。
Release them all! Everything we have prepared for auction!
♪♪～
ガルルル…
あっ…。
These are the infamous Maurenian Saber-Tooth Tigers.
（ファティマー）猛毒を持つ
マウレニアサーベルタイガーよ。→
気をつけて。
Be careful now.
A slight graze from their fangs or their claws means instant death!
牙や爪にかすっただけで
即死だからね。
おねえちゃん…。
Miss...
全然　大丈夫よ。
Don't worry about a thing.
Yes, everything will be okay.
≪そう　大丈夫≫
♪♪～
Because my legs and my body
≪なぜなら　私の脚は…→
体は…　誰よりも　何よりも→
are faster, sharper, and stronger than anyone else's!
速い！　鋭い！≫
≪そして　強い！≫
♪♪～
I am a Fanalis.
≪私は　ファナリス≫
≪大陸の覇者　最強の戦闘民族≫
One of the rulers of the Dark Continent.
One of the strongest warrior tribes!
うわぁ～！
くっ…。
うわぁ～！　あっ！　あっ　あっ…。
お手上げだわ。　奴隷商として→
I give up.
I made a mistake as a slave hunter when I captured you.
奴隷を買い損ねた　私のミスね。
殺されても　しかたない。
It's only natural if you want to kill me.
鍵を下さい。
えっ？
Give me the key.
What?
捕まっている人たちを逃がします。
I am going to free all of the people you have captured.
What! Do you feel bad for them?
何よ！　情けをかけたつもり!?
奴隷のくせに…。
Even though you're no better than a slave yourself!
私は　もう　奴隷ではありません。
I am no longer a slave.
ドゴン！
（一同）あっ！
What's going on? Who are you?
≪なんだ？　なんだ？　あんた。
Please leave this place.
逃げてください。
鍵は　この中にあります。
Here are the keys.
≪あっ！
≫おお～！
ナージャ！
あっ　お母さん　お父さん！
Nadja!
Mommy! Daddy!
ナージャ！　うぅ…。
早く　薬を　お願いします。
She needs medicine.
おい　薬は　どこだ？
（ナージャ）怖かったよ…。
Yes! Where is the medicine?
I was scared...
Is it in that bag?
≫（アラジン）おねえさん
あのときの　おねえさんかい？
Miss?
Are you the lady from back then?
ん？　あっ。
Found it!
Hurry!
You are!
やっぱり
あのときの　おねえさん！
あなたは…。
You...
Do you know her, Aladdin?
アラジン　知り合いか？
うん。　ほら→
Yeah. She's the strong lady I was telling you about!
前に話した　強いおねえさんさ。
Why is someone as powerful as you being held captive?
あなたみたいな強い人が
どうして捕まってるんですか？
キャラバンに
大きな岩を落とされちゃったんだ。
A huge rock fell on our caravan.
I lost consciousness and when I opened my eyes again, here I was.
そのまま僕は　気を失っちゃって→
気付いたら
みんなと一緒に　こうなってて。
In chains along with everyone else.
This way, Boss!
≫（盗賊）こっちです　お頭！
≫（Ｓナンド）絶対に逃がすな！
Don't let a single one get away!
まずいぞ。
アラジン　これ　お前のだろ？
This is bad.
Aladdin, this is yours, right?
♪♪～
I owe you! Thank you for hiring
mercenaries to help bring back one of my own.
恩に着るぞ。
俺の仲間を奪い返すために→
傭兵を雇ってくれるとは。
友人のキャラバンを
見捨てられないからな。
I could never abandon a friend's caravan.
こら～！　ライラ　サアサ！→
What are you doing, Leila! Sahsa!
お前たちは　宿で待ってろと…。
（ライラ）そうはいくかよ。→
I told you two to wait at the inn!
As if we could do that!
モルジアナも
捕まってるかもしれないんだ。
Morgiana could be in trouble!
Help! A giant!
（盗賊）助けて～！
（盗賊）巨人が～！
なんだ？
盗賊たちか？
What was that?
The thieves?
♪♪～
Let's get out of here!
（盗賊）逃げなきゃ！
（盗賊）誰か～！
Someone help me!
大丈夫　心配ない。　あれは…。
Don't worry! He's on our side!
おねえさん　久しぶりだね～！
It's been so long, miss!
（ライラ）変わってないな　お前。
And you haven't changed a bit.
So that mysterious boy was Aladdin after all.
不思議な少年とは
この方のことだったんですね。
I met them in the village I was in before I met Alibaba!
アリババくんに出会う前の町で
知り合ったのさ。
I've missed this feeling!
懐かしい感触だよ～。
（ライラ）いいかげんにしろ！
That's enough!
I'm surprised you know him too, Morgiana! What a coincidence!
（サアサ）それにしても　モルジアナも
知り合いだったなんて→
すごい偶然。
≪（隊商長）そうでもないぞ。
It's not a coincidence. Travels will
reunite old friends from near and far.
旅の途中　思わぬ友人との再会は
あるものだ。
へっ！　俺たちのようにな。
Just like us.
This is great. Now we can go to Balbadd.
（隊商長）よかったな
バルバッドに行けるぞ。
あれ？　モルジアナさんも
バルバッドへ行くの？　僕もだよ。
Morgiana, you're going to Balbadd too?
I am too!
（ヒゲ隊商長）こいつは　チーシャンには
会いたいヤツがいないって→
This guy said that the person he was looking for wasn't in Qishan, so he's headed to Balbadd to find him.
バルバッドへ
行くことになったんだ。
アリババさんのこと…。
Is that person Alibaba?
Yeah. Let's travel together!
ちょうどいい。　一緒に行こうよ。
♪♪～
異論はありません。
I have no objections to that.
♪♪～
（２人）ははははっ。
ははっ。
ふふふっ。
（一同）あははははっ！
≫コツ　コツ　コツ…
あっ。
You know, everything in the world is actually connected.
あのね　世界は
実は　つながっているんだって。
That means that, even if we get separated, we'll never be alone.
だから　たとえ離れてしまっても→
みんな　一人じゃない。
大切な人とは　いつまでも→
The bonds we have with those close to us keep us connected always.
ずっと
どこかで　つながっているのさ。
≪あのとき…≫
I'm sure that was him...
≪確かに　ゴルタスの声が
聞こえた気がした≫
I'm sure it was Goltas' voice that helped me.
♪♪～
See you!
じゃあね！
絶対　また会おうな！
We'll definitely meet again!
うん　またね～！
Yeah! See you!
♪♪～
じゃあ　行こう。
はい。
Let us get going too!
Yes.
I'm happy to be traveling with you again, Morgiana.
これからも
よろしくね　モルジアナさん。
Yes.
はい。
ねえ　「モルジアナさん」って→
Morgiana's kind of a long name. Do you mind if I use a nickname?
長いから　なんて呼ぼうか？
なんとでも。
I don't mind.
じゃあ　モッさん。
Then I'll call you Mor!
Is that okay?
嫌かい？
いえ…。
Yes. It is.
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
me ni mieru sekai ha subete kako no monogatari sa
The world you see before your eyes is a story already told.
♪♪～
kagayaku mirai wo miushinau na yo
Don't lose sight of the bright future ahead.
♪♪～
kimi ni ha motto ippai yume to kibou ga arun da
You're destined to realize great hopes and dreams.
bootto shitetara minogashichau zo
But if you blink for too long, they'll leave you behind.
♪♪～
dekinai riyuu sagasu yori
Instead of searching for an excuse,
yatte mireba ii
why not just give it a try?
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
yubi to yubi wo marume ryoume ni ate
Make circles with your fingers and put them around your eyes.
imeeji shite sagashiteru mono
Picture your hopes and dreams!
♪♪～
atama no naka no adobenchaaa
Picture your personal adventure story!
doko he mukau?
Where are you headed?
yubi bouenkyou
What can you see
♪♪～
yubi no sono sukima ni nani ga mieru?
in the space between your fingers?
tooi you demo hontou ha chikai
It might seem far, but it's really not.
yogen no you na takaramono
It's a promise as valuable as any treasure!
I am the man who has conquered seven dungeons.
I am Sinbad, high king of the seven seas!
Yes, that's great. Now put some clothes on please, Sin.
7th Night
His Name is Sinbad
Next time: His Name is Sinbad.
Oh man, he's so awesome!
（シンドバッド）
俺が　７つの迷宮を攻略した男→
七海の覇王　シンドバッドさ。
（ジャファール）いいから
早く　服を着てください　シン。
（アリババ）なんか　すごいの　きた～！
野田総理が、近いうちに信を問う
と
発言してから３カ月。
今日、東京都内で衆議院の解散時
期について
自身の中では既に決めているのか
と
問われた総理は、心の中も明かし
ませんとして
明言を避けた。